let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Every time a fault slips or moves, the earth quakes.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Fault is a series of variations at the earth's surface produced by the sudden release of energy by movement along the earthquakes.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Most faults produce repeated displacements over geologic time.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Faults produce quakes when friction between the two sides of a fault keeps it from moving until the stress on the fault overcomes the friction, then the fault slips and creates an earthquake.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Reverse Fault is a dip-slip fault in which the block above the fault has moved downward relative to the block below.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Strike-slip fault is a dip-slip fault in which the upper block, above the fault plane, moves up and over the lower block. This type of faulting is common in areas of compression.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The San Andreas Fault is an example of a right lateral fault.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The Earth's crust is like the shell of an egg; it is the thickets of the Earth's layers.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Four types of stresses affect the Earth's crust: compression, tension, shear and confining stress.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Tension stress is a type of stress that causes the rocks to push or squeeze against one another.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Some scientists think shear stress caused the ancient, massive continent Pangaea to break off into the seven continents we have today.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "When compression stress occurs, the force of the stress pushes some of the crust in different directions.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "When confining stress happens, the crust compacts, which makes it look smaller.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Normal Fault is a fault on which the two blocks slide past one another.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Energy from Earth's interior makes the ground move.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },

    ]